Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Friendship Rekindled
Episode 55
The energy shield is about to close.
Let’s rush through while we can.
Everyone’s here; it’s time to spring the trap.
Bear, swat them away!
The one responsible for destroying everyone’s world,
I’m going to stop you.
Watch this!
Amazing!
We need to hurry.
It’s so beautiful here.
Could this be…
This is the garden in the painting.
It’s the world of Pink’s dreams.
The device is over there. Let’s go.
Where did you pests come from? Trying to eat my flowers?
Pink, it’s me.
Whoever you are,
get out of here right now!
Bear.
Trespassing on my manor—unforgivable!
Pink, didn’t we agree
to save your world together?
This is my world.
Aren’t these Colorful Dandelions your favorite?
Why destroy them?
Because, being here…
even if shattered,
they can gather together again
and be reborn.
Bear!
Let’s hurry to the Absorption Device.
No one is leaving this place.
Bear!
You guys go—I’ll hold her off here.
No, we can’t leave you behind.
Don’t worry, I’ll come find you soon.
Alright, it’s a promise.
This is the underground city.
Welcome
to
my new world.
What’s going on here?
The robots here have all been taken over by Peach.
Watch out!
I’ll go stop her.
Then I’ll cover you.
Peach, wake up!
Xiao Mei…
Got any other tricks?
My friends will definitely stop you.
Really?
It looks like your friends won’t be making it here.
It’s you guys…
What happened to them?
Give them back to me!
Give back Sparky,
Paddi,
and Tibbie—
Give them back.
Enough said. That’s what happens to anyone
who tries to stop our plan.
Now it’s your turn.
You…
What exactly are you doing?
Of course—
we’re here to stop you,
Everyone is here.
It’s great that you’re all safe.
I promised you I would come find you.
What exactly is going on?
How did you manage to break free from Blue’s control?
Brown, come to your senses.
Enough talk.
Stop! We aren’t enemies.
Anyone who intrudes on my world is an enemy.
Pink, take a good look around you.
These flowers were all stolen.
Get out of here right now!
Is that all you’ve got?
Watch this.
Mere child’s play.
Oh no.
Didn’t you say I was your second friend?
Friends don’t hurt friends.
Second friend…
Brown, have you forgotten the promise you made to Brother Dahuang
to protect your village?
Weren’t you trying to restore the garden of your dreams?
Pink, their home and their roots don’t belong here.
And this is certainly not the world of your dreams.
Take a good look at them.
The dandelions are so beautiful.
It’s so beautiful here.
This is their true home.
Please remember—Brother Dahuang is waiting for you to come back.
Brown, don’t forget the promise we made.
The delicious food we shared, the scenery we admired together…
are all proof of our friendship.
Stop it.
Please, wake up.
Pink! Thank goodness, you’re awake.
Thank you.
Peach, come to your senses.
You traitors who’ve turned against your own kind…
Stop being so deluded.
They will definitely help you break free from Blue’s control.
I will absolutely not be swayed by you.
Peach, have you forgotten
what you’ve always stood for?
You’re supposed to save your original world.
Do you remember what we said inside the black hole?
Don’t give up hope.
I, my friends,
and everyone in this world.
If we all join forces,
we can definitely save this colorful world.
A colorful world…
Yes, try to remember, Peach.
Give me a little more time; I can save this world.
Peach, wake up!
Thank you.
Welcome back, Peach.
To be continued